snorgtees.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy | SnorgTees

Welcome to SnorgTees.com (the “Website”), owned and published by Digital Basement, LLC ("we" or "us"). We have developed this Privacy Policy to explain the types of information we collect from users of the Website, the reasons we collect this information, and how we utilize this information once we have collected it. By accessing the Website, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy.

#### **Types of Information Collected**

**Information You Provide to Us**

We collect information you provide to us through the Website, including your name, email address, residential address, shipping address, phone number, credit card information, product preferences and selections, purchase history, reviews of our services and products, and demographic information.

**IP Address and Device Information**

We collect information from your Internet browser when you visit our Website, including your IP address, HTTP referrer, browser and device information, webpages visited, session information, and search queries on our Website. We collect this information using cookies and other tracking technologies. Users who do not accept cookies may not be able to access all areas or features of the Website. We also use Google Analytics on our Website. Google Analytics uses cookies and other tracking technologies to monitor how you interact with our Website and other websites. We use Google Analytics to obtain generalized information about our customers and visitors to our Website. The information collected by Google Analytics is stored by Google and is subject to Google’s privacy policy, which is accessible on Google’s website.

#### **How We Use Your Information**

We may use the information we collect for a variety of purposes, including:  
● Processing payments and fulfilling product purchases and returns;  
● Facilitating, personalizing, and improving your experience on the Website;  
● Providing customer service;  
● Monitoring and analyzing usage of the Website, and optimizing its performance;   
● Improving security of the Website and preventing fraud;   
● Making business improvements and managing inventory;  
● Delivering targeted advertising; and  
● Communicating with you, including sending you marketing materials and newsletters to your email address and mailing address (we use MailChimp to manage some of our email messaging to you, and you can access MailChimp’s privacy policy [here](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)).

#### **How We May Share Your Information**

We do not sell your information. We may share your personal information with our vendors, service providers, business partners, and other third parties as reasonably necessary to operate the Website and provide services to you, including but not limited to processing payments and fulfilling product purchases (including shipping orders), improving the Website, performing maintenance on the Website, providing technical support, communicating with you, and optimizing the relevance of our messages to you. We may also share the information we collect to comply with the law, a court order, or legal process served on us, to cooperate with the investigation of alleged unlawful conduct, to enforce the Terms of Use or protect the intellectual property and other rights associated with the Website, or to transfer our assets to another company. We also partner with search engine providers (e.g., Google, Bing, and Yahoo), advertising networks (e.g., Google), and social media providers (e.g., Facebook, Instagram, and Pinterest) to deliver targeted advertising for our products. The advertisements you see on these platforms may be based on information you provide to us and information collected by us or by them through cookies and other tracking technologies that monitor how you interact with our Website. These providers may combine that information with information they collect or obtain from other sources. We also participate in affiliate advertising programs that allow websites to earn revenue for advertising our products. You can find out more information about opting out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative website: http://optout.networkadvertising.org and the Digital Advertising Alliance website: optout.aboutads.info. 

#### **Your Rights in Your Information**

We process your personal information with your consent, as necessary to process payments and fulfill product purchases and returns, and in furtherance of the legitimate interests our business, including to prevent fraud, provide customer service, optimize the Website, market our products, make business improvements, and manage inventory. The personal information we collect from you will be transferred to and stored and processed in the United States. Depending on your location and our basis (or bases) for collecting your personal information, you may be entitled to certain privacy rights, including:  
● Right of access to your personal information;  
● Right to rectification of your personal information;  
● Right to erasure (“right to be forgotten”);  
● Right to restrict processing of your personal information;  
● Right to data portability;   
● Right to object (opt-out); and  
● Right to withdraw consent. 

#### **Security**

We take commercially reasonable measures to safeguard the information we collect from you. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, please contact us.

#### **Retention**

We will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the information was collected as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

#### **Children**

The Website is not targeted to or intended for use by children, and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from anyone under the age of 13. We will delete any information in our database that we determine originates from a child under the age of 13. If you are 13 years of age or older but under the age of 18, you may only access the Website under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian and subject to his or her consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. You must be 18 years of age or older to create an account with us.

#### **Revisions to Privacy Policy**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may share it. Any modification is effective as of the posting of the change.

#### **Contact Us**

We are the controller of your personal information that you provide to us or that we collect through the Website. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personal information, or to access, modify, or erase your personal information pursuant to applicable law, please contact us using the information provided below.

Mailing Address:

SnorgTees  
Attn: Legal / Privacy  
1200 Northmeadow Parkway, Suite 120  
Roswell, GA 30076

Email: privacy@snorgtees.com

This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 4, 2018.
